moola.com 2008-02-12

# Privacy Policy Page

_**Moola Corporation

Privacy Policy - April 10th, 2001

**_

**

Privacy Policy

**

This Privacy Policy applies to the "Moola.com" and "Moola.ca" websites (collectively, the "website") owned and operated by RND Technologies SRL, its parents, subsidiaries, affiliates, assigns, successors and related entities (collectively, "Moola", "we", "us", or "our"). 

**

Purpose of this Policy

**

Moola believes that you should understand how we use the information you provide and furthermore that you should have the right to approve the use of that information. In handling of your information Moola follows a policy of "informed consent". Please take a few minutes to read our complete privacy statement so you can understand how information is used and the specific measures we take to protect your personal information. This page describes the policies of our company regarding any information we receive about you while visiting the website. Moola intends this policy to reduce uninvited use of your personal information. 

**

Website Usage Data

**

We collect and store typical web server log data about your use of the website during your visit to the website. Examples of this type of data are: the name of your Internet service provider, the site that referred you to us, any pages you request, and the time and date of those requests etc. We use this information to generate statistics and measure site activity to benefit the website users. This same information may be shared with third parties in order to provide our services or to analyze, store, or aggregate the information. It may also be shared with other third parties, working with us to improve the services of Moola or this website. **Any data that we share with third parties is anonymous and can never be linked to you (see below).**

We want you to get the most out of the website and to trust that we make every effort to protect your confidentiality. Personal information is either requested or required on many areas of the website to verify your identity, to customize your experience, and to ensure that you qualify to use particular sections of the site. The amount and type of information we collect depends on how you use our site and how much information you wish to provide. The information will be stored and used in order to enhance our relationship with you.

**

Collection of Personally Identifiable Information

**

When registering, using the "My Account" area of the website, and when answering skill-testing questions about ads, you may provide personal information (such as name, contact information, or other registration or personal information) to Moola. Moola uses this personal information in an aggregate and anonymous form to allow advertisers to target specific consumer groups while keeping your identity confidential. For example, if you tell us that you are 25 years old and live in a certain city, you will see ads which are targeted to your age and geographic area. 

Moola may share anonymous information about you with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties. However, we only divulge aggregate information about our users and will not share personally identifiable information with any third party without your express consent. Moola will not disclose your personal information, except as described herein, and Moola will not disclose information to others that would connect any personal information with your actual identity unless Moola is compelled to by law or as necessary to enforce your agreements with us. In our sole discretion we still reserve the right to make exceptions, whenever we believe an emergency, illegal activity or some other reasonable basis exists for notifying or providing such information to the appropriate authorities.

You may review your personal information at your "Personal Profile" page. There you can modify information that is incorrect or delete information. Information that can be modified includes your password and email address. We keep a history of changed information to investigate suspected fraud with your account.

**

Communication With You

**

Moola believes very strongly in your rights to be free from unwanted communications. We believe that you have the right to control the use of your information. Moola shall never provide your email information to any third party without your express permission. We will only use your contact information to verify your identity, to communicate with you regarding transactions, special promotions, events and policy changes, or in an emergency.

**

Cookies

**

In addition, Moola may place information on your computer in the form of "cookies" to customize your experience of Moola's site. A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored within your browser when you visit a cookie-enabled website. As you browse the Web, cookie-enabled sites will send cookies to your browser, along with pages. Your browser probably has options that will let you control whether the browser accepts cookies, rejects cookies, or notifies you each time a cookie is sent to you.

If your browser is set to reject cookies, cookie-enabled websites will not recognize you when you return. This provides you with anonymity, but it also makes it very difficult to offer you customized services. It is also less secure than using cookies, because all of your specific data must be sent to the website each time you view a page. Accepting cookies means your private data can stay at the Web server, and the only information transmitted over the Internet is your ID cookie.

If your browser is set to accept cookies, any cookies that are sent to your browser are stored in your computer for a period of time. There are a few different types of cookies. A "session" cookie is stored only in your computer's working memory (RAM) and only lasts for your browsing session. When you close all of your browser's windows, or when you shut down your computer, the session cookie disappears forever. A "permanent" cookie is stored on your computer's hard drive until a specified date, which could be tomorrow, next week, or 10 years from now. Permanent cookies stay on your computer until either they expire, they are overwritten with newer cookies, or until you manually remove them.

**

Privacy Statement Revisions

**

Moola reserves the right to change this policy. While we will indicate material changes by posting a prominent notice on our site, users can also check here to see if a revised policy has been posted. If our policy materially changes, the information we currently have in our files will be subject to the modified policy. You will be notified of a material change in our privacy policy through a notice posted on our Web site.
